<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://support.whitehill.club/blog</id>
    <title>Whitehill Group Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://support.whitehill.club/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Whitehill Group Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://support.whitehill.club/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axon's release!]]></title>
        <id>https://support.whitehill.club/blog/axon-release</id>
        <link href="https://support.whitehill.club/blog/axon-release"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing our new, reworked Axon whitelisting system!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<admonition type="note"><p>We're trialling the blog functionality. This section of the website may not exist forever.</p></admonition>
<p>👋 Hej! Welcome to Axon.</p>
<p>We're pleased to announce that the reworked version of our revolutionary Axon whitelisting system is released as of today!</p>
<p>You are now able to purchase products for Robux via the <a href="https://www.roblox.com/games/13188104119/Whitehill-Group-Product-Hub">Product Hub</a> and via GBP (Stripe) on the <a href="https://axon.whitehill.club/">Axon website</a>.</p>
<p>There are still a lot of features missing from the website, and we're planning to roll out more management options for your JSM licences, so that you can reallocate which Roblox user can utilise your licences. Along with this, we have many more exciting features planned, so stay tuned!</p>
<p>To continue using your gamepass licences, you must head over to the <a href="https://www.roblox.com/games/13188104119/Whitehill-Group-Product-Hub">Product Hub</a> and hit the "Migrate licences" button in the bottom left. This will transfer your gamepass licences over to the new Axon database.</p>
<p><strong>What's next?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>We're looking to phase out product distribution on Discord, so you'll see less people with the product roles, and people will be advised to download their products from the <a href="https://axon.whitehill.club/">Axon website</a> instead.</li>
<li>Users with &lt;13 Roblox accounts are currently unable to sign into Axon. We're looking into alternative sign in methods for these users only.</li>
</ul>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Gale</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/NotAlex7331</uri>
        </author>
        <author>
            <name>Alyx</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/TheCakeChicken</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="axon" term="axon"/>
        <category label="product-release" term="product-release"/>
    </entry>
</feed>